Guide to the Stanford University, Freshman Information Office, Records SC0321
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
Stanford University, Freshman Information Office, records
1968-1983
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
Stanford University. Freshman Information Office.
SC0321
18 Linear Feet
Information about Access
The materials are open for research use.
Stanford University. Freshman Information Office.
- Records, Accession ARCH-1985-028
  Conditions Governing Access note
  The materials are closed for 75 years from date of creation. Audio-visual materials are not available in original format, and must be reformatted to a digital use copy.
  - Freshman Correspondence 1979 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Norm and Resident Fellow Letters, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Frosh Info 1979 Vol. 2 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Freshman Correspondence 1978 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Frosh Correspondence 1981 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Frosh Housing, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Freshman Information Housing, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Freshman Processing: 1980-81, 1980-1981 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Freshman Processing Printouts, 1972 (Box 4)
  - Freshman Processing Printouts, 1975-1976 (Box 4)
  - Freshman Processing Printouts, 1976-1977 (Box 5)
  - Freshman Processing Printouts, 1977-1978 (Box 5)
  - Frosh Info 1983 WICS Men (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Information cards (Box 6)
  - Frosh Info 1983 WICS Women (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Freshman Processing (1 of 2), 1979-80 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Freshman Processing (2 of 2), 1979-80 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Freshman Processing, 1981 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Freshman Information, 1981 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Housing Letters to Entering Freshmen, 1981 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Freshman Correspondence 1977 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Freshman Processing and Correspondence 1978 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Freshman Information 1978 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Freshman Information 1982-1983 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Freshman Processing 1981-1982 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Freshman Information 1977 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Freshman Processing 1976 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Freshman Correspondence 1980 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Frosh Housing 1980 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Frosh Info 1979 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Freshman Processing 1980 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Freshman Processing, 1968-69 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Freshman Processing, 1972-73 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Freshman Processing - Housing File, 1972-73 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Freshman Housing Floor Charts, 1973-74 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Freshman Processing, 1974-75 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Freshman Processing, 1975-76 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Freshman Information, 1980 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Frosh Processing 1973-1974 (Box 13)
  - Freshman Roster 1974-1975 (Box 14)